Office of the Provost. Administrative files of Ernest Carroll Moore. 1917-1936. UARC.0261
UCLA Library Special Collections
Office of the Provost. Administrative files of Ernest Carroll Moore.
1917-1936
UCLA Library Special Collections
Office of the Provost
UARC.0261
26.4 Linear Feet (66 boxes)
Record Series 261 contains the administrative files of Ernest C. Moore, University Chancellor from 1919-1936. Files include correspondence, office memoranda, minutes, agendas, reports, applications, budget requests and statements. Subjects covered by the files include administration of the of the university, schools, colleges, and academic departments; business conducted by the Academic Senate, administrative offices at the University of California, Berkeley, and the Associated Students and other campus student organizations; student activism and disciplinary action; and general correspondence between the chancellor and students and faculty.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9935211883606533
Historical Note
The title of the chief executive of the school now known as UCLA has changed many times since the school's 1919 inception as the Southern Branch of the University of California. Beginning in 1919, the Los Angeles campus was administered by the director. In 1930, the tile of this position was changed to vice president and director; and later, in 1931, to vice president and provost. From 1945-1948, the chief executive officer was called provost of the University and, in 1948, vice-president and provost. In 1952, chancellor became the official title of the office. During the periods 1942-1945 and 1950-1952, UCLA was administrated by a three-man committee.
Ten men have served as chief executive at UCLA since 1919 when the Los Angeles State Normal School became a part of the University of California System:
Director and Provost Ernest Carroll Moore (1919 – 1936)
Provost Earle Raymond Hedrick (1937-1942)
Provost Clarence Addison Dykstra (1945-1950)
Chancellor Raymond Bernard Allen (1952-1958)
Chancellor Vern Oliver Knudsen (1959)
Chancellor Franklin David Murphy (1960-1968)
Chancellor Charles Edward Young (1969-1997)
Chancellor Albert Carnesale (1997 – 2006)
Acting Chancellor Norman Abrams (2006 – 2007)
Chancellor Gene Block (2007 – Present)
Scope and Content
Record Series 261 contains the administrative files of Ernest C. Moore, University Chancellor from 1919-1936. Files include correspondence, office memoranda, minutes, agendas, reports, applications, budget requests and statements. Subjects covered by the files include administration of the of the university, schools, colleges, and academic departments; business conducted by the Academic Senate, administrative offices at the University of California, Berkeley, and the Associated Students and other campus student organizations; student activism and disciplinary action; and general correspondence between the chancellor and students and faculty.
This is an inactive record series; no additional University records are expected to be added.
- Academic Senate., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the Faculties., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Administration, Berkeley - Examiner., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Administration, Berkeley - Recorder of the Faculties., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Admissions., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Committees., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Advisory Administrative Board., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- California State Normal Schools., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Canfield Memorial., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Dean - Summer Session., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Deans - Counselor of Women., 1917-1920. (Box 1)
- Department - Art., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Department - Chemistry., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Department - English., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Departments - Biology., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Departments - Commerce., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Departments - Education, Psychology, and Philosophy., 1919-1920. (Box 1)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., 1927-1928. (Box 2)
- Department - Extension., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Geography and Geology., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - History., 1918-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Languages, Romanic., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Mechanical Department., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Music., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Physics., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Training Department., 1918-1920. (Box 2)
- Departments - Vocational Education Division., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Education - State Offices., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Faculty - Application for Position at the Southern Branch., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Faculty - Resumes of Southern Branch Faculty., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- General Correspondence., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Memorial Meeting for Jesse F. Millspaugh., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Regents., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1919-1920. (Box 2)
- Academic Senate., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Administration, Berkeley - Examiner., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the Faculties., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Administration, Berkeley - Director of Vocational Education., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Business Office, Budget Statements., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Committee., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Admissions., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Advisory Administrative Board., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Alumni., 1920-1921. (Box 3)
- Canfield Memorial., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Constitutional Amendment, No. 12., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Department - Art., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Department - Education and Philosophy., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Annual Report of Ernest C. Moore., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Biology., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Commerce., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - English., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Geography., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Geology and Mineralogy., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - History., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Languages, Romanic., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Mechanical Department., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Medical Department, Los Angeles., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Music., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Phsyical Education for Women., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Physics., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Political Science., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Psychology., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Training Department., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Departments - Vocational Education Division., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Education - City and Country Offices., 1920-1921. (Box 4)
- Academic Senate., 1921-1922. (Box 5)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1921-1922. (Box 5)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the Faculties., 1921-1922. (Box 5)
- Administration, Berkeley - Educational Relations, Head of., 1921-1922. (Box 5)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1921-1922. (Box 5)
- Education - State Offices., 1920-1921. (Box 5)
- General Correspondence., 1920-1921. (Box 5)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1920-1921. (Box 5)
- Regents., 1920-1921. (Box 5)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1920-1921. (Box 5)
- Administration Souther Branch - Business Office., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Berkeley - Readers and Helpers Roll., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Berkeley - Recorder., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Berkeley - General Correspondence., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Advisoroy Administrative Board., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Business Office, Budget Statements., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Committees., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Comptroller's Office., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Recorder., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Assistant Director., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Secretary, Appointments., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Deans - Counselor of Women., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Department - Commerce., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Art., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Biology., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Education., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - English., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Extension., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Geography., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Geology and Mineralogy., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - History., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1921-1922. (Box 6)
- Department - Physics., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Department - Political Science., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Languages, Romanic., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Library., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Mechanical Department., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Philosophy and Psychology., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Training Department., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Departments - Vocational Education Division., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Education - State Offices., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1921-1922. (Box 7)
- Academic Senate., 1922-1923. (Box 8)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1922-1923. (Box 8)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the College of Letters and Science., 1922-1923. (Box 8)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the Faculties., 1922-1923. (Box 8)
- Administration, Berkeley - Educatinal Relations, Head of., 1922-1923. (Box 8)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., Jul -Dec, 1922. (Box 8)
- General Correspondence., 1921-1922. (Box 8)
- Housing Report., 1921-1922. (Box 8)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1921-1922. (Box 8)
- Memorial Fund, Jesse Millspaugh., 1921-1922. (Box 8)
- Publicity - Statements for Newspapers., 1921-1922. (Box 8)
- Regents., 1921-1922. (Box 8)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1921-1922. (Box 8)
- Survey - Size (Acreage) of Select US Campuses., 1921-1922. (Box 8)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., Jan - Jun, 1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office, Annual Report., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Berkeley - Readers and Helpers Roll., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Berkeley - Recorder., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Berkeley - General Correspondence., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Administration Staff Meetings., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Admissions., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Advisory Administrative Board., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Committees., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Recorder., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Adminstration, Southern Branch - Secretary, Executive., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Deans - Women., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Departments - Art., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Departments - Biology., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Departments - Commerce., 1922-1923. (Box 9)
- Department - Mathematics., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Department - Music., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Education., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - English., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Geography., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Geology., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - History., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Languages, Romanic., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Library., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Physics., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Political Science., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Training Department., 1922-1923. (Box 10)
- Departments - Vocational Education Division., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- Education - State Offices., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- General Correspondence., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- Memorial Fund, Jesse Millspaugh., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- Regents., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- Students - U.S.C. Affair., 1922-1923. (Box 11)
- Academic Senate., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the College of Letters and Science., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the University., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Berkeley - Assistant Dean of the University., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Berkeley - Director of Vocational Education., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Berkeley - Examiner., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Berkeley - Readers and Helpers Roll., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Berkeley - Recorder., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Berkeley - General Coresspondence., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Admissions., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Committees., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administrative, Southern Branch - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1923-1924. (Box 12)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Administration, Southern Branch-Budget, Est. Based on 600-1000 Add. Students., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Examiner., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Recorder., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Committee on Research, Survery Forms., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Alumni., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Conferences., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Deans - Women., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Deapartments - Annual Report of Ernest C. Moore., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Department - Economics., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Department - English., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Department - Geography., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Department - Geology., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Department - History., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Departments - Arts., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Departments - Biology., 1922-1923. (Box 13)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Departments - Education., 1923-1924. (Box 13)
- Department - Home Economics., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Department - Military Science and Tatics., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Department - Physics., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Language, Classical., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Language, Romanic., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Library., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Music., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Philosophy and Psychology., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Political Science., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Departments - Training Department., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Education - State Offices., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Memorial Fund, Jesse Millspaugh., 1923-1924. (Box 14)
- Academic Senate., 1924-1925. (Box 15)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1924-1925. (Box 15)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the University., 1924-1925. (Box 15)
- General Correspondence., 1923-1924. (Box 15)
- Regents - Board to Servey Southern Branch Regarding Need for a Fourth Year., 1923-1924. (Box 15)
- Regents - General Correspondence., 1923-1924. (Box 15)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1923-1924. (Box 15)
- Veterans' Bureau., 1923-1924. (Box 15)
- Administration, Berkeley - Assistant Dean of the University., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1923-1924. (Box 16)
- Administration, Berkeley - Readers and Helpers Roll., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Berkeley - Recorder., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Berkeley - General Correspondence., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Admissions., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Advisory Administration Board., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Committees., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Examiner., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Recorder., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Secretary, Executive., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Council of the Southern Branch., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Alumni., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Conference., 1924-1925. (Box 16)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Deans - Women., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Department - Biological Sciences., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Department - Education., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Department - English., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Department - Geology., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Department - History., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Department - Political Science., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Arts., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Economics., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Geography., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Language, French., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Languages, Spanish., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Library., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Music., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Departments - Physics., 1924-1925. (Box 17)
- Academic Senate., 1925-1926. (Box 18)
- Administration, Berkeley - Comptroller's Office., 1925-1926. (Box 18)
- Department - Training Department., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Departments - General Correspondence., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Departments - Psychology., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Education - City and Country Offices., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Education - State Offices., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- General Correspondence., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Memorial Fund, Jesse Millspaugh., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Regents., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Students - Fraternities and Sororities., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1924-1925. (Box 18)
- Administration, Berkeley - Dean of the University., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Berkeley - Assistant Dean., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Berkeley - Readers and Helpers Roll., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Berkeley - Recorder., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Berkely - General Correspondence., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Advisory Administration Board., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Committees., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Examiner., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Recorder., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Secretary, Appointment., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Secretary, Executive., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Admissions., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Administration, Southern Branch - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1925-1926. (Box 19)
- Alumni., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Conferences., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Deans - Men., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Deans - Women., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Annual Report of Ernest C. Moore., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Art., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Biological Science., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Economics., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Education., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - English., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Geopgraphy., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - History., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Languages, French., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Languages, Spanish., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Library., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Library, Clark., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1925-1926. (Box 20)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1925-1926. (Box 20)